

Get in touch!

Mobile:

+38(097)-307-07-11

Skype:

svlugovoy

Email:

svlugovoy@gmail.com

Website:

serhiiluhovyi.github.io

Linkedin:

<u>linkedin.com/in/svlugovoy/</u>

Education

National Aviation University

Kyiv, Ukraine

September 2015 – June 2017 Master's degree in Computer science

Kremenchuk State Polytechnical University

Kremenchuk, Ukraine September 1998 – May 2003 Master's degree in Engineering

Foreign languages

English:

Upper-Intermediate

Ukrainian, Russian:

Native

Certificates

AWS Certified Developer DVA-Co1

Jul 01, 2020 - Jul 01, 2023

Kubernetes Certified Application Developer CKAD

Jul 23, 2020 - Jul 23, 2023

Serhii Luhovyi

Senior Java Developer

Summary

I am a software developer with robust problem-solving skills and proven experience in creating and designing software in a construction, medical, e-commerce and telecom domains.

In my free time I like to travel, visit the gym and take courses on Udemy.

Technical Background

Architecture: microservices oriented, monolithic

Web Services: RESTful

Frameworks: Spring (Boot, Cloud, MVC, Data JPA/JDBC, Security),

Hibernate

DBs, tools: MySQL, PostgreSQL, MS SQL Server, Oracle, Flyway

Messaging: RabbitMQ, Kafka

CI/CD: Gradle, Maven, Gitlab CI, Jenkins, Bamboo

Version Control: Git, Mercurial, svn **Testing:** Junit, Mockito, Jacoco

Web: JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML/CSS, Angular, React

Cloud: AWS, GCP, Pivotal Cloud Foundry Monitoring: ELK, Grafana, Prometheus Infrastructure: Docker, Kubernetes, Helm

Work Experience

Senior Java Developer

Intellectsoft (Kyiv, Ukraine) | December 2019 - Present

Project description: ERP system for the third-largest civil engineering and construction company in Norway

Technologies: Java11, Spring Boot, Hibernate, Spring Data JDBC, React, REST, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Jenkins, GitLab Cl, Git, Gradle, Docker,

Kubernetes, Helm, AWS

Senior Java Developer

Synergetica (Kyiv, Ukraine) | August 2019 - September 2019

Project description: Secure, easily implementable infrastructure that helps healthcare organizations manage patients remotely on a large scale at a fraction of the current costs

Technologies: Java 11, Spring Boot, Hibernate, Spring Data JPA, AngularJS, REST, MySQL, Kafka, RabbitMQ, Jenkins, Git, Maven, Docker, Kubernetes, GCP

Senior Java Developer

GlobalLogic (Kyiv, Ukraine) | October 2018 - July 2019

Project description: Projects for a medical device manufacturer, one of the world leaders in the sleep care industry

Technologies: Java 7/8, Spring Boot, Spring Cloud, Hibernate, Spring Data JPA, Spring JdbcTemplate, JSP, REST, MS SQL Server, ActiveMQ, Jetty, JBoss, Bamboo, Git, Maven, Splunk, Pivotal Cloud Foundry

Middle Java Developer

Epam (Kyiv, Ukraine) | October 2017 - September 2018

Project description: E-commerce solutions for one of the largest international retail group in beauty and household goods industry for European market (online stores in different European countries)

Technologies: Java 7/8, Hybris, Spring MVC, Spring Security, JSP, Docker, REST, Oracle, MySQL, RabbitMQ, Tomcat, Gradle, Jenkins, Git, svn

Java Developer

GlobalLogic (Kyiv, Ukraine) | May 2016 - September 2017

Project description: Project of one of the leaders telecom industry, flexible system of phone numbers management for national telecom operators

Technologies: Spring Boot, Spring MVC, Spring JdbcTemplate, JSP, SOAP, Oracle, H2, WebLogic, Git, Gerrit, Maven, Jenkins

Software Engineer (Front-end, Java)

Freelance (Kremenchuk, Kyiv, Ukraine) | April 2014 - May 2016

Project description: Websites for local businesses, B2B solution for small businesses

Technologies: Spring Boot, Hibernate, MySQL, Maven, Bootstrap, WordPress

System Administrator/Technician/Business owner

ArtFox (Kremenchuk, Ukraine) | May 2004 - September 2015

Project description: Custom canvas prints and design solutions **Technologies:** WordPress, Photoshop, MySQL, UkrSklad